Consuela	NOUN	B-PERS
Ms.	NOUN	O
Ms.	NOUN	O
She	PRON	O
Ms.	NOUN	O
A	DET	O
She	PRON	O
Separately	ADV	O
Mr.	NOUN	B-PERS
He	PRON	O
Mr.	NOUN	B-PERS
As	ADV	O
Peter	NOUN	B-PERS
Former	ADJ	O
Earlier	ADV	O
In	ADP	O
And	CONJ	O
Several	ADJ	O
One	NUM	O
Another	DET	O
In	ADP	O
But	CONJ	O
For	ADP	O
Clinton	NOUN	B-PERS
Among	ADP	O
Separately	ADV	O
The	DET	O
Washington	NOUN	B-ORG
Washington	NOUN	B-GPE
Washington	NOUN	B-GPE
currently	ADV	O
Washington	NOUN	B-GPE
graduate	NOUN	O
has	VERB	O
.	.	O
Newman	NOUN	I-PERS
would	VERB	O
Bentsen	NOUN	I-PERS
early	ADV	O
Tarnoff	NOUN	B-ORG
Sen.	NOUN	O
.	.	O
addition	NOUN	O
Time	NOUN	B-ORG
appointees	NOUN	O
is	VERB	O
likely	ADJ	O
the	DET	O
Robert	NOUN	B-PERS
many	ADJ	O
officials	NOUN	O
others	NOUN	O
.	.	O
current	ADJ	O
.	.	O
.	.	O
's	PRT	O
is	VERB	O
and	CONJ	O
of	ADP	O
been	VERB	O
Clinton	NOUN	B-PERS
.	.	O
report	VERB	O
.	.	O
as	ADP	O
.	.	O
Tim	NOUN	O
the	DET	O
.	.	O
magazine	NOUN	O
of	ADP	O
Bernadine	NOUN	B-PERS
holdover	NOUN	O
offfice	NOUN	O
Kyle	NOUN	I-PERS
subcabinet	NOUN	O
are	VERB	O
expected	VERB	O
the	DET	O
briefing	NOUN	O
a	DET	O
44	NUM	O
candidacy	NOUN	O
a	DET	O
Mr.	NOUN	B-PERS
Harvard	NOUN	B-ORG
a	DET	O
transition	NOUN	O
who	PRON	O
directly	ADV	O
who	PRON	O
today	NOUN	O
a	DET	O
Wirth	NOUN	O
Colorado	NOUN	B-ORG
Joan	NOUN	B-PERS
columnist	NOUN	O
President	NOUN	O
Healy	NOUN	I-PERS
is	VERB	O
of	ADP	O
.	.	O
jobs	NOUN	O
said	VERB	O
to	PRT	O
incoming	VERB	O
room	NOUN	O
longtime	ADJ	O
years	NOUN	O
is	VERB	O
counsel	NOUN	O
Dingell	NOUN	I-PERS
Law	NOUN	I-ORG
congressional	ADJ	O
officials	NOUN	O
would	VERB	O
to	PRT	O
headed	VERB	O
.	.	O
former	ADJ	O
is	VERB	O
Democrat	NOUN	I-ORG
Spero	NOUN	I-PERS
Strobe	NOUN	B-PERS
Bush	NOUN	B-PERS
.	.	O
David	NOUN	B-PERS
U.S.	NOUN	B-GPE
the	DET	O
.	.	O
to	PRT	O
be	VERB	O
Clinton	NOUN	B-PERS
could	VERB	O
House	NOUN	B-ORG
old	ADJ	O
being	VERB	O
to	PRT	O
have	VERB	O
School	NOUN	I-ORG
staffer	NOUN	O
said	VERB	O
be	VERB	O
Treasury	NOUN	B-ORG
the	DET	O
the	DET	O
Carter	NOUN	B-PERS
expected	VERB	O
had	VERB	O
.	.	O
Talbott	NOUN	I-PERS
are	VERB	O
director	NOUN	O
Kessler	NOUN	I-PERS
Trade	NOUN	O
Senate	NOUN	B-ORG
the	DET	O
be	VERB	O
hired	VERB	O
administration	NOUN	O
be	VERB	O
staffer	NOUN	O
.	.	O
championed	VERB	O
the	DET	O
been	VERB	O
.	.	O
since	ADP	O
that	ADP	O
giving	VERB	O
Secretary-designate	NOUN	O
Senate	NOUN	B-ORG
Clinton	NOUN	B-PERS
administration	NOUN	O
to	PRT	O
been	VERB	O
an	DET	O
is	VERB	O
likely	ADJ	O
of	ADP	O
.	.	O
Representative-designate	NOUN	O
Finance	NOUN	I-ORG
list	NOUN	O
deciding	VERB	O
include	VERB	O
is	VERB	O
used	VERB	O
and	CONJ	O
would	VERB	O
by	ADP	O
committee	NOUN	O
considered	VERB	O
Ms.	NOUN	O
1979	NUM	O
Frank	NOUN	B-PERS
up	PRT	O
Lloyd	NOUN	B-PERS
Finance	NOUN	I-ORG
camp	NOUN	O
official	NOUN	O
get	VERB	O
a	DET	O
executive	ADJ	O
to	PRT	O
to	PRT	O
the	DET	O
head	NOUN	O
Mickey	NOUN	B-PERS
Committee	NOUN	I-ORG
of	ADP	O
between	ADP	O
Kitty	NOUN	B-PERS
seriously	ADV	O
for	ADP	O
an	DET	O
be	VERB	O
several	ADJ	O
.	.	O
allies	NOUN	O
Washington	NOUN	B-GPE
.	.	O
Newman	NOUN	I-PERS
a	DET	O
Bentsen	NOUN	I-PERS
Committee	NOUN	I-ORG
is	VERB	O
and	CONJ	O
a	DET	O
leading	VERB	O
vice	NOUN	O
be	VERB	O
stay	VERB	O
National	NOUN	B-ORG
of	ADP	O
Kantor	NOUN	I-PERS
's	PRT	O
candidates	NOUN	O
recently	ADV	O
Higgins	NOUN	I-PERS
considering	VERB	O
staff	NOUN	O
